freegamepick.com 2018-12-17

# Privacy Policy at FreeGamePick

**Overview of Our Privacy Policy**

We supply free entertainment and utility software including games software. (We refer to our software and Products throughout this agreement as our "Services").

We offer our Services to you in exchange for your agreement to view promotions, advertisements, or participate in other offers. 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our online privacy practices regarding:

Information we collect  
How we use the information  
How we share your information, if at all  
Your choices

We may make available shorter versions of this Privacy Policy. We also may supplement this policy for specific Services. Where there is a conflict between this policy and our summary this policy will govern. Where there is a conflict between this policy and our supplement, the supplement will govern.

We may change this privacy policy. If we change this policy we will post the changes to this privacy statement, our websites' homepages, and other places we deem appropriate. We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you use our site, navigate around out site, register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience--Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.  
To improve our website--We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
To provide targeted advertisements.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that sites and service providers may transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. They enable the site and service provider systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. You can turn off cookies in your settings at any time.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

We may use Cookies to provide a targeted advertising experience on and off our site.   
**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other's rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Multi-site Advertising**

We have online Behavorial Advertising on our Site.

Advertisers and advertising networks use tracking technologies to collect information about users' computers or mobile devices and their online activities (for example, web pages visited and searches made) as well as general geographic location and use that information to display targeted ads to users. We sometimes allow these ad companies to collect such information when you use our sites and apps to enable them to display targeted ads to you on and off our Site.

Many ad companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative. NAI members allow users to opt out of being tracked by cookies. To opt out of cookie tracking by NAI members, you may visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/ and click on the "Consumer Opt-out" button. Companies may also be members of the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") and to opt out of cookie tracking by DAA members, you may visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.   
Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Opt-Out**

We currently do not send messages to or collect data from users. If at any time we do contact you, it would only be for support reasons. If in that regard, you would like stop receiving messages or notifications, you can click on an unsubscribe link from any message we provide to no longer receive our messages.

If you would like to be removed from our system, you can reach us via email at contactus@freegamepick.net.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account via the "Sign In" link on the top right of the home page. Then click on 'Page Settings' and then go to the 'Account' section. 

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms & Conditions**

Please also visit our "Terms of Service" section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Terms Of Service.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified February 9, 2015.

**Contact Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may Contact Us at:

FreeGamePick 2825 E Cottonwood Pkw. #500  
Salt Lake City, UT 84121  
(801) 447-2333  
contactus@freegamepick.net
